floralinvestment.com 2016-12-21

# Privacy policy

We understand that business is successful only if customers trust the company. Our activity is impossible without collecting a certain amount of customer information. We hereby inform you about the types of the information, as well as our actions with it, how to make changes and amendments to the information provided by you.

Pay special attention to the fact that this policy can only be applied to websites belonging Floralinvestment. It may not apply to websites of organizations and individuals mentioned in the link or banner on our website.

## Information collected

When you register to open a demo trading account or gather some information about you. This is done to the administrative and/or legal purposes and to improve service quality. The following information ( "Information about you") to collect and store:

Personal information: name, address, e-mail. mail, etc. ( "Personal Information") shall not be disclosed for security reasons.

In addition, we store information about traffic to the website and the IP-address.

All data about you is stored and processed only in accordance with the laws of confidentiality of personal information that apply to international jurisdiction, Floralinvestment.com, in which you have registered. To learn more, please see below "Disclosure of Personal Information" section.

## Disclosure of personal information

Employees, directors, officers and / or representatives of Floralinvestment are required to maintain the confidentiality of your data. They can in no way transmit or use any information about you without good reason.

The complete protection against all acts of your data. An exception can only be cases where the data are disclosed administrative and judicial authorities, when required by applicable international law, or if you have given a written agreement on the disclosure of such information. In the latter case, you can at any time to change or cancel such consent.

Without prejudice to the provisions set forth above, Floralinvestment may disclose the following information in specific cases:

General information about the customer, such as name, email address. mail, etc., if they are necessary to companies carrying out administrative tasks for Floralinvestment.

For general information about the corporate clients as a professional secret financial institutions to provide marketing consulting services.

## Familiarization with the information

According to the provisions of international law on the treatment of personal information of any customer Floralinvestment. He has the right to know what information is available at Floralinvestment about him / her.

If the information about you available to us proves to be inaccurate or outdated, we will contact you immediately upon your request.

## THE FREE NEWSLETTER AND MAILING LIST

Upon confirmation that you would like to join our newsletter, we will from time to time send you free information relating to the products we market, general advice related to online marketing, and promotional material for other products. You may unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time.

## PURCHASE AGREEMENT

When you sign up, we collect your name, phone number and e-mail address and may use this with a small number of third parties who we are working closely with. In particular, we may share your data with coaching partners who offer a related service to our own (where you have agreed to this).

## HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

To provide you with information, products or services (and updates to our service) that you request from us or which we feel may interest you and to carry out our obligations to you.

## DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985 or our associated companies.

## WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes.

You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## ACCESS TO INFORMATION

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.
